A Guide to the Trust for Mutual Understanding records FA412
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1970, 1975, 1978, 1982, 1987-2012; 3; 45.95 Cubic Feet 121 letter document boxes
  - Center for International Theatre Development, New Drama Materials, Miscellaneous, DF-0528, 2004-2005 (Box 45, Folder 498)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, B-0706, B-0800, 2006-2008 (Box 45, Folder 499)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, Miscellaneous, B-0706, B-0800, 2006-2007 (Box 45, Folder 500)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, Miscellaneous, B-0706, B-0800, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 501)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, Miscellaneous, B-0706, B-0800, Teatr Zar, Grotowski Institute, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 501)
  - Center for International Theatre Development: Bulgaria, B-0859, 2008-2010 (Box 45, Folder 502)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, Bulgaria, B-0859, Visual Police, Director: Javor Gardev (Box 45, Folder 502)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, Bulgaria, B-0859, Z I F T, Director: Javor Gardev, Screenwriter: Vladislav Todrov, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 502)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, Bulgaria, B-0859, Directing Selections, Director: Javor Gardev, 1999-2007 (Box 45, Folder 502)
  - Center for International Theatre Development, Bulgaria, B-0859, Metropolis, Director: Javor Gardev, ARTE TV (Box 45, Folder 502)
  - Center for Puppetry Arts, DF-0122, 2001, 2003, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 503)
  - Center for Puppetry Arts, DF-0202, 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 504)
  - Center for Puppetry Arts, DF-0408, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 505)
  - Center for Puppetry Arts, DF-0818, 1989, 1999, 2006-2008 (Box 46, Folder 506)
  - Center for Puppetry Arts, Miscellaneous, DF-0818, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 507)
  - Center for Puppetry Arts, Miscellaneous, DF-0818, Anton Andele, Traditional Puppet Theatre, 2008 February 12 (Box 46, Folder 507)
  - Center for Resource Management, B-0710, 1996, 1999, 2002, 2006-2009 (Box 46, Folder 509)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, B-0145, 1999-2003 (Box 46, Folder 509)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, B-0353, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 510)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, B-0353, ICA Crimean Chersonesos, Ann Rep & Website, 2004 January 12 (Box 46, Folder 510)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, B-0353, Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, TMU-Photos (Box 46, Folder 510)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, Miscellaneous, B-0353, 2003-2004 (Box 46, Folder 511)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, B-0453, 2004-2007 (Box 46, Folder 512)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, B-0453, Center for the Study of Anciet Territories, Institute of Classical Archaeology, University of Texas, Austin, Chersonesis, Seuestopol, & Kyiv, Photos, 2005 May-June (Box 46, Folder 512)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, B-0546, 2005-2007 (Box 46, Folder 513)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, Miscellaneous, B-0546, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 514)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, Miscellaneous, B-0546, Chora Park Visitor Center, Visualization, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 514)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, B-0756, 2007-2009 (Box 46, Folder 515)
  - Center for Study of Ancient Territories, ICA Photos to TMU, Institute of Classical Archaeology, University of Texas, Austin, 2008 December (Box 46, Folder 515)
  - Center for the Study of Ancient Territories, Miscellaneous, B-0756, 2006, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 516)
  - Center for Sustainable Future, B-0104, 2000-2001, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 517)
  - Central and East European Art Founadtion, DF-0643, 2004-2008 (Box 47, Folder 518)
  - Central and East European Art Foundation, DF-0643, Dominik Lang (Box 47, Folder 518)
  - Central and East European Art Foundation, Miscellaneous, DF-0643, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 519)
  - Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, EC-0213, 2002-2004 (Box 47, Folder 520)
  - Chashama, DF-0527, 2004-2006 (Box 47, Folder 521)
  - Chashama, DF-0527, Currency, Chashama, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 521)
  - Choros International Projects, EC-0305, 2002-2004 (Box 47, Folder 522)
  - Choros International Projects, EC-0305, Final Report and Pictures - Choros International Project, 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 522)
  - Choros International Projects, B-0411, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 523)
  - Circumpolar Conservation Union, EC-0515, 2005-2008 (Box 47, Folder 524)
  - City Center, Boris Eifman Ballet, B-0282, 2001-2004, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 525)
  - City Center, DF-0206, 2002, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 526)
  - City Center, Boris Eifman Ballet, EC-0610, 2005-2008 (Box 48, Folder 527)
  - City Center, Boris Eifman Ballet, EC-0610, City Center, Eifman Ballet of St. Petersburg, Photos (Box 48, Folder 527)
  - City Center, Boris Eifman Ballet, Miscellaneous, EC-0610, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 528)
  - Collision Theory, DF-0137, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 529)
  - Collision Theory, Miscellaneous, DF-0137, 2000, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 530)
  - Collision Theory, DF-0301, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 531)
  - Colorado Ballet, B-0189, 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 532)
  - Columbia University, The University Seminars, DF-0302, 2002-2006 (Box 48, Folder 533)
  - Columbia University, The University Seminars, DF-0302, Columbia Black Sea, Conference Photos (Box 48, Folder 533)
  - Columbia University, Harriman Institute, DF-0730, 2005, 2007, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 534)
  - Complexions Contemporary Ballet, B-0860, 2008-2009 (Box 48, Folder 535)
  - Continuum, B-0354, 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 536)
  - Continuum, EC-0604, 2006-2007 (Box 48, Folder 537)
  - Continuum, B-0757, 2001, 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 538)
  - Creative Connections, B-01111, 2000-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 49, Folder 539)
  - Creativity 21st Century, EC-0202, 20022003, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 540)
  - Crude Accountability, B-0575, 2005-2007 (Box 49, Folder 541)
  - Crude Accountability, B-0670, 2006-2008 (Box 49, Folder 542)
  - Crude Accountability, B-0670, Crude Accountability, Photos for Final Report, 2008 February (Box 49, Folder 542)
  - Crude Accountability, B-0670, Photos from Taman, Russia, 2008 August 1 (Box 49, Folder 542)
  - Crude Accountability, B-0774, 2007-2009 (Box 49, Folder 543)
  - Crude Accountability, B-0774, Photos of Taman (Box 49, Folder 543)
  - Crude Accountability, B-0878, 2008-2009 (Box 49, Folder 544)
  - Cultural Hungarica Foundation, B-0861, 2008-2009 (Box 49, Folder 545)
  - Cultural Hungarica Foundation, Miscellaneous, B-0861, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 546)
  - Cultural Hungarica Foundation, Miscellaneous, B-0861, Underground Music From Behind the Iron Curtain, 2009 November 6-7 (Box 49, Folder 546)
  - Cultural Survival, DF-0628, 2004, 2006-2008 (Box 49, Folder 547)
  - Cultural Survival, DF-0628, Totem Project, 2007 May 14 (Box 49, Folder 547)
  - Czech Center, DF-0636, 2005-2007 (Box 49, Folder 548)
  - Czech Center, DF-0636, ARCHA Photos (Box 49, Folder 548)
  - Da Capo Chamber Players, B-0314, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 549)
  - Da Capo Chamber Players, B-0412, 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 550)
  - Da Capo Chamber Players, Miscellaneous, B-0412, 1997, 2002, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 551)
  - Da Capo Chamber Players, B-0508, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 552)
  - Da Capo Chamber Players, B-0715, 2006-2008 (Box 50, Folder 553)
  - Dance Advance, B-0355, 2001-2005 (Box 50, Folder 554-555)
  - Dance Advance, B-0454, 2004-2007 (Box 50, Folder 556)
  - Dance Advance, B-0454, Dance Advance (Box 50, Folder 556)
  - Dance Advance, DF-0403, 2004-2005 (Box 50, Folder 557)
  - Dance Advance, B-0716, 2006-2010 (Box 50, Folder 558)
  - Dance Advance, B-0716, Photos from Dance Advance (Box 50, Folder 558)
  - Dance Advance, B-0716, Dance Advance, Dada Image/Anna Dvozdowski (Box 50, Folder 558)
  - Dance Advance, Miscellaneous, B-0716, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 559)
  - Dance Films Association, DF-0304, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 560)
  - Dance Films Association, DF-0410, 2004-2005 (Box 51, Folder 561)
  - Dance Films Association, B-0547, 2005-2008 (Box 51, Folder 562)
  - Dance Films Association, B-0547, Charles Abbott, Video Movement, Light, Alla Korgan, Deborah Lefkowitz, Pro Arte, 2006 May (Box 51, Folder 562)
  - Dance Films Association, B-0813, 2008-2009 (Box 51, Folder 563)
  - Dance Films Association, B-0813, Kinodance, Stills, 2008-2009 (Box 51, Folder 563)
  - Dance Films Association, Miscellaneous, B-0813, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 564)
  - Dance New Amsterdam, B-0862, 2008-2009 (Box 51, Folder 565)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, B-0190, 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 566)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, B-0283, 2002-2003, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 567)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, B-0315, 2002-2004, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 568)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, B-0356, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 569)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, B-0455, 2004-2006 (Box 51, Folder 570)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, Miscellaneous, B-0455, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 571)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, B-0548, 2005-2207 (Box 52, Folder 572)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, B-0614, 2005-2007 (Box 52, Folder 573)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, B-0614, Dance Theater Workshop, Photos Julieta Cervantes, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 573)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, B-0707, 2006-2009 (Box 52, Folder 574)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, B-0803, 2007-2009 (Box 52, Folder 575)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, Meeting Points, B-0814, 2007-2009 (Box 52, Folder 576)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, Witness Relocation, B-0815, 2006-2009 (Box 52, Folder 577)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, Witness Relocation, B-0863, 2008-2009 (Box 52, Folder 578)
  - Dances We Dance, DF-0326, 2002-2004 (Box 52, Folder 579)
  - Dances We Dance, DF-0326, Dances We Dance, Photos of Duncan Center, Prague (Box 52, Folder 579)
  - Dancing in the Streets, B-0316, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 580)
  - Danspace Project, B-0242, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 581)
  - Danspace Project, B-0317, 2002-2004 (Box 52, Folder 582)
  - Danspace Project, B-0317, Romanian Independent Dance, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 582)
  - Danspace Project, B-0549, 2003, 2005-2007 (Box 52, Folder 583)
  - Danspace Project, B-0758, 2007-2010 (Box 53, Folder 584)
  - Danspace Project, B-0758, Vicky Shick Dance Theater Workshop, Repair, Plum House, 2007 February 22 (Box 53, Folder 584)
  - Danspace Project, B-0758, Dada von Bzdulow Theatre Variation No XII (documentary) (Box 53, Folder 584)
  - David Dorfman Dance, B-0657, 1993, 1998, 2000, 2002-2009 (Box 53, Folder 585)
  - David Dorfman Dance, B-0759, 2007-2009 (Box 53, Folder 586)
  - David Parker and the Bang Group, DF-0135, 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 587)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, B-0146, 1999-2002 (Box 53, Folder 588)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, DF-0230, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 589)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, DF-0319, 2002-2006 (Box 53, Folder 590)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, DF-0319, Denver Zoological Foundation, Camel Photos (Box 53, Folder 590)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, DF-0444, 2004-2006 (Box 53, Folder 591)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, DF-0444, Denver Zoological Foundation, Mongolia Wildlife Conservation Project, Argali Lamb Capture Photos (Box 53, Folder 591)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, B-0572, 2005-2008 (Box 53, Folder 592)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, B-0572, Denver Zoological Foundation, Mongolian Wildlife Conservation Program, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 593)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, B-0572, Denver Zoological Foundation, Mongolian Wildlife Conservation Project: Small Carnivores & Local Management of Protected Areas (Box 53, Folder 592)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, B-0775, 2007-2010 (Box 53, Folder 593)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, B-0775, Mongolian Wildlife Conservation Project, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 593)
  - Denver Zoological Foundation, B-0775, Denver Zoo Photos for the Trust for Mutual Understanding, 2008 (Box 53, Folder 593)
  - Dickinson College, B-0164, 2000-2003 (Box 54, Folder 594-595)
  - Dickinson College, B-0164, Photos Promoting NGO-University Partnerships, Russian/American Exchange, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 594)
  - Digital Independence, DF-0314, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 596)
  - DOCOMOMO, DF-0425, 2004-2006 (Box 54, Folder 597)
  - DOCOMOMO, Miscellaneous, DF-0425, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 598)
  - Double Edge Theatre, B-0122, 2000-2001, 2006-2007 (Box 54, Folder 599)
  - Double Edge Theatre, B-0211, 2000-2002, 2006-2007 (Box 54, Folder 600)
  - Double Edge Theatre, B-0243, 2001-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 54, Folder 601)
  - Double Edge Theatre, EC-0306, 2003-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 54, Folder 602)
  - Double Edge Theatre, EC-0306, DET Picture for TMU, Don Quixote (Box 54, Folder 602)
  - Double Edge Theatre, B-0456, 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 603)
  - Double Edge Theatre, EC-0407, 2003-2004, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 604)
  - Double Edge Theatre, EC-0504, 2004-2007 (Box 55, Folder 605)
  - Double Edge Theatre, EC-0504, Double Edge Theatre, Photo from the UnPOSSESSED (Box 55, Folder 605)
  - Double Edge Theatre, B-0615, 2005-2007 (Box 55, Folder 606)
  - Double Edge Theatre, B-0615, Double Edge Theatre, Photos, 2006-2007 (Box 55, Folder 606)
  - Double Edge Theatre, B-0615, Photos from Double Edge Theatre (Box 55, Folder 606)
  - Double Edge Theatre, Miscellaneous, B-0615, 2005-2006 (Box 55, Folder 607)
  - Double Edge Theatre, B-0717, 2005, 2007-2009 (Box 55, Folder 608)
  - Doug Varone and Dancers, DOVA, Inc., EC-0511, 2000-2007 (Box 55, Folder 609)
  - The Drawing Center, DF-0639, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 610)
  - The Drawing Center, Miscellaneous, DF-0639, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 611)
  - Isadora Duncan International Institute, DF-0138, 2001-2003 (Box 55, Folder 612)
  - Dusan Tynek Dance Theatre, B-0658, 2005-2008 (Box 56, Folder 613)
  - Early Music Foundation, DF-0234, CANCELLED, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 614)
  - Earth Day Network, B-0262, 2002-2004 (Box 56, Folder 615)
  - Earth Day Network, B-0370, 2003-2007 (Box 56, Folder 616)
  - Earth Day Network, B-0529, DF-0630, 2003-2008 (Box 56, Folder 617)
  - Earth Day Network, DF-0510, 2005-2006 (Box 56, Folder 618)
  - Earth Day Network, DF-0614, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 619)
  - Earth Day Network, B-0741, DF-0738, 2006-2008 (Box 56, Folder 620)
  - Earth Day Network, B-0879, 2008-2009 (Box 56, Folder 621)
  - Earth Island Institute, B-0105, 1999-2002, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 622)
  - Earth Island Institute, B-02101, 2002-2003, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 624)
  - Earth Island Institute, B-0433, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 625)
  - Earth Island Institute, Center for Safe Energy, B-0434, 2004-2007 (Box 57, Folder 626)
  - Earth Island Institute, B-0530, 1999, 2004-2006 (Box 57, Folder 627)
  - Earth Island Institute, B-0573, 2005-2007 (Box 57, Folder 628)
  - Earth Island Institute, Center for Safe Energy (CSE), Altai Project, B-0639, 2004-2007 (Box 54, Folder 629)
  - Earth Island Institute, B-0742, 2007-2009 (Box 57, Folder 630)
  - Earth Island Institute, B-0840, 2008-2009 (Box 57, Folder 631)
  - Earth Island Institute, Altai Strawbale, DF-0802, 2006-2009 (Box 57, Folder 632)
  - EarthCorps, B-0333, 2002-2004, 2006 (Box 57, Folder 633)
  - EarthCorps, B-0333, EarthCorps, Russian Tech Photos, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 633)
  - EarthCorps, B-0531, 2004-2006 (Box 57, Folder 634)
  - EarthCorps, B-0640, 2005-2008 (Box 57, Folder 635)
  - EarthCorps, Miscellaneous, B-0640, 2005, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 636)
  - EarthCorps, B-0776, 2007-2009 (Box 57, Folder 637)
  - Earth Corps, B-0880, 2007-2010 (Box 57, Folder 638)
  - Earthjustice Legal Defense Fund, B-0106, 2000-2002, 2006-2007 (Box 58, Folder 639)
  - Earthjustice, B-0334, 2002-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 58, Folder 640)
  - East Coast Artists, DF-0225, 2002-2203, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 641)
  - East Coast Artists, B-0659, 2006-2008 (Box 58, Folder 642)
  - East European Folklife Center, DF-0218, 2001-2003 (Box 58, Folder 643)
  - East European Folklife Center, DF-0516, 2005, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 644)
  - East European Folklife Center, B-0616, 2000, 2002, 2005-2006, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 645)
  - Eastern National, B-0413, 2003-2008 (Box 58, Folder 646)
  - Eastern National, Miscellaneous, B-0413, 2007 (Box 58, Folder 648)
  - Echo Park Film Center, B-0718, 2006-2007 (Box 58, Folder 648)
  - Echo Park Film Center, B-0718, Ukrainian Film Tour Stills, 2007 July (Box 58, Folder 648)
  - Echo Park Film Center, B-0718, Ukrainian Film Tour Images, 2007 July (Box 58, Folder 648)
  - Ecologia, B-0263, 2002-2003, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 649)
  - Ecologia, DF-0406, 2004, 2006, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 650)
  - Ecologia, DF-0708, 2006-2007, 2009 (Box 58, Folder 651)
  - The Ecology Center, B-0166, 2001-2003 (Box 59, Folder 652)
  - The Ecology Center, B-02102, 2002-2004 (Box 59, Folder 653)
  - The Ecology Center, B-02102, The Ecology Center, DSCN0659 (Box 59, Folder 653)
  - Eiko & Koma, B-0123, 1993-2001 (Box 59, Folder 654)
  - Eiko & Koma, Caravan Project, B-0191, 2000-2002 (Box 59, Folder 655)
  - Eiko & Koma, Inta Inc., DF-0411, 2002-2004, 2007-2008 (Box 59, Folder 656)
  - Elko & Koma, DF-0621, 2005-2008 (Box 59, Folder 657)
  - Eiko & Koma, DF-0820, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 658)
  - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships, DF-0327, 2002-2004 (Box 59, Folder 659)
  - E-LAW (Environmental Law Alliance Worldwide), DF-0132, 2000-2002 (Box 59, Folder 660)
  - E-LAW (Environmental Law Alliance Worldwide), B-02103, 2002-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 59, Folder 661)
  - E-LAW (Environmental Law Alliance Worldwide), B-0372, 2003-2004 (Box 59, Folder 662)
  - E-LAW (Environmental Law Alliance Worldwide), EC-0416, 2004-2005 (Box 59, Folder 663)
  - E-LAW (Environmental Law Alliance Worldwide), B-0576, 2005-2007 (Box 60, Folder 664)
  - E-LAW (Environmental Law Alliance Worldwide), DF-0651, 2006-2007 (Box 60, Folder 665)
  - E-LAW (Environmental Law Alliance Worldwide), B-0777, 2007-2008 (Box 60, Folder 666)
  - E-LAW (Environmental Law Alliance Worldwide), B-0881, 2008-2009 (Box 60, Folder 667)
  - E-LAW (Environmental Law Alliance Worldwide), Miscellaneous, B-0881, 2009 (Box 60, Folder 668)
  - Electronic Music Foundation, B-0457, 2003-2005 (Box 60, Folder 669)
  - Electronic Music Foundation, Philip Glass to Malta Festival, Miscellaneous, B-0457, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 670)
  - Electronic Music Foundation, B-0617, 2005-2008 (Box 60, Folder 671-672)
  - Electronic Music Foundation, B-0617, Malta 2006 "Americana Na Malicie" Concert, Photos (Box 60, Folder 671)
  - Elaine Kaufman Cultural Center, DF-0113, 1990, 200-2001, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 673)
  - Elisa Monte Dance, B-0244, 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 674)
  - Environmental Defense, B-0264, 2001-2003 (Box 61, Folder 675)
  - Environmental Defense, Miscellaneous, B-0264, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 676)
  - Environmental Defense, EC-0319, 2002-2003 (Box 61, Folder 677)
  - Environmental Defense, B-0436, 2003-2005 (Box 61, Folder 678)
  - Environmental Defense, Miscellaneous, B-0436, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 679)
  - Environmental Defense, B-0574, 2004-2007 (Box 61, Folder 680)
  - Environmental Film Festival, DF-0418, 2004-2005 (Box 61, Folder 681)
  - Environmental Film Festival, Miscellaneous, DF-0418, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 682)
  - Environmental Health Network, B-02106, 2002-2004 (Box 61, Folder 683)
  - Environmental Health Network, B-0371, 2003-2005 (Box 62, Folder 684)
  - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, EC-0200, 2002, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 685)
  - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, EC-0212, 2002-2003, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 686)
  - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, DF-0807, 2008-2010 (Box 62, Folder 687)
  - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, DF-0807, 1 CD
  - Experimental Intermedia, DF-0718, 2006-2007, 2009 (Box 62, Folder 688)
  - Experimental Intermedia, EIF in Russia, Pics for TMU (Box 62, Folder 688)
  - Experimental Intermedia, DF-0742, 2007-2009 (Box 62, Folder 689)
  - Experimental Intermedia, DF-0742, Trust Videos, Prague, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 689)
  - Experimental Intermedia, DF-0742, Trust Fotos, Prague, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 689)
  - Eyes and Ears Foundation, B-0414, 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 690)
  - Faberge Arts Foundation, "New Uses for Old Buildings", B-0124, 2000-2001 (Box 62, Folder 691)
  - Faberge Arts Foundation, DF-0237, 2002-2004, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 692)
  - The Field, DF-0512, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 693)
  - The Field, DF-0542, 2005-2007 (Box 62, Folder 694)
  - The Field, DF-0542, Yasna Voices on Bulgarian National TV, 2006 August-September (Box 62, Folder 694)
  - The Field, DF-0542, Yasna Voices, Audio Recording, Symphony Space, 2006 November 18 (Box 62, Folder 694)
  - The Field, DF-0542, Grant Report (Box 62, Folder 694)
  - The Field, Barabara Bickart, DF-0622, 2006, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 695)
  - The Field, Barbara Bickart, DF-0622, The Field, Barbara Bickart, Images for Queer Normal, 2005; 2011:012:091 (Box 62, Folder 695)
  - The Field, Yanira Castro, DF-0716, 2002, 2005, 2007, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 696)
  - The Field, Yanira Castro, DF-0716, The Field, Yanira Castro, Photos of Dark Horse/Black Forest (Box 63, Folder 696)
  - Film Arts Foundation, DF-0812, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 697)
  - The Film Society of Lincoln Center, B-0284, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 698)
  - The Film Society of Lincoln Center, DF-0536, 2005-2006 (Box 63, Folder 699)
  - The Film Society of Lincoln Center, DF-0613, 2006, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 700)
  - Film Society of Lincoln Center, Miscellaneous, DF-0613, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 701)
  - Flaherty International Film Seminars, DF-0713, 2006-2008 (Box 63, Folder 702)
  - Flaherty International Film Seminars, DF-0713, The Flaherty/IFS Elena Kolikova Photos (Box 63, Folder 702)
  - Flaherty International Film Seminars, DF-0822, 2008-2009 (Box 63, Folder 703)
  - The Flea Theater, DF-0430, 2001, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 704)
  - Forest Trends, B-0167, 2000-2001, 2006-2007 (Box 63, Folder 705)
  - FotoFest International, B-0192, 1996, 2000-2003 (Box 63, Folder 706)
  - FotoFest International, Miscellaneous, B-0192, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 707)
  - FotoFest International, B-0318, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 708)
  - FotoFest International, B-0318, FotoFest, Images from Russia, TMU Report, 2003 June (Box 64, Folder 708)
  - FotoFest International, EC-0401, 2003-2005 (Box 64, Folder 709)
  - FotoFest International, EC-0401, Images for TMU Annual Report, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 709)
  - FotoFest International, B-0550, 2004-2007 (Box 64, Folder 710)
  - FotoFest International, B-0550, FotoFest, TMU Funded Guests, 2006 March (Box 64, Folder 710)
  - FotoFest International, EC-0806, 2006-2009 (Box 64, Folder 711)
  - FotoFest International, Miscellaneous, EC-0806, 2006-2008 (Box 64, Folder 712)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, B-0001, B-0003, B-0182, B-0272, 1999-2002, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 713)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Community Revitalization Expert Advisors Program, 2000-2001, B-0168, 2000-2001, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 714)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Ladislav Sutnar, B-0193, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 715)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Ladislav Sutnar Exhibition, Miscellaneous, B-0193, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 716)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Chalupecky Catalogue, DF-0103, 2000-2001, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 717)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Chalupecky Catalogue, Miscellaneous, DF-0103, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 718)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Museum of Decorative Arts, DF-0137, 2000-2001 (Box 65, Folder 719)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Americana II, EC-0103, 2000-2003 (Box 65, Folder 720)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Young Visual Artist Award, Serbia and Croatia, Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 721)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Young Visual Artist Award, B-0216, 2002-2003, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 722)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Young Visual Artist Award, B-0216, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 723)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, DF-0200, 2003, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 724)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society: Award Program Travel, DF-0201, 2001-2002, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 725)